{"version": 2.0, "questions": [{"question": "Which is Not a fundamental mode of heat transfer", "answers": {"a": "Conduction", "b": "Convection", "c": "Radiation", "d": "All"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "c", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Pure conduction can be observed in,", "answers": {"a": "Solids", "b": "Liquids", "c": "Gases", "d": "None"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "a", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Large number of free electrons are present in,", "answers": {"a": "Metals", "b": "Non metals", "c": "Metaloids", "d": "All"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Free electrons move in the direction of", "answers": {"a": "heat flow", "b": "temperature gradient", "c": "Random", "d": "None"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Number of free electrons present in wood are", "answers": {"a": "zero", "b": "abundant", "c": "few", "d": "Not known"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "The temperature gradient in the direction f heat flow is", "answers": {"a": "positive", "b": "zero", "c": "negative", "d": "None"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Thermal conductivity of metals is high due to their", "answers": {"a": "melting point", "b": "strength", "c": "free electrons", "d": "All"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Thermal conductivity of good insulator is", "answers": {"a": "large", "b": "small", "c": "medium", "d": "Any"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "In steady state, the rate of conduction is not a function of", "answers": {"a": "Temperature", "b": "time", "c": "direction", "d": "All"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}, {"question": "Which is Not a unit of Thermal conductivity.", "answers": {"a": "W/mk", "b": "W/m", "c": "W/mC", "d": "Kcal/cm C"}, "explanations": {"a": "", "b": "", "c": "", "d": ""}, "correctAnswer": "b", "difficulty": "beginner"}]}